The world outside is sharp, my love
The air is full of harm
You don't need to lift a finger Just stay here
safe and warm Don't you worry about your buttons
Don't you worry about your shoes Mother's here
to do it for you
It's the least that we can do
This is the system of care I'll be your hands I'll
be your hair You don't need to move You don't need
to think Just stay right here My love and drink
The comfort and the danger for you
It's all you know
It's all that's true
The doctors try to scare you
With needles and with pills
They do not know your body
They do not know your ills
I'll be your only medicine
I'll know just what you need
I'll keep you safe and pure, my boy
My perfect friend, you'll see This
is the loom, the system of care I'll open your
hands, I'll open your air You don't need to move
You don't need to think Just stay right here My
love and drink The comfort in the cage I built for
you It's
all you know
It's all that's true
The bed is cold, I know You hate to sleep alone
Just come and comfort, mother My flesh and of my
bone You're all I have, you see You'll never be
apart You'll always be right here with me My own
This
is the The system of care I'll be your hands I'll
be your air You don't need to move You don't need
to think Just stay right here My love and drink
The comfort in the cage I built for you
It's all you know
It's all that's true
It's all you